A Finding Aid to the Lee Nordness business records and papers, circa 1931-1992 (bulk 1954-1984), in the Archives of American Art AAA.nordlee
Archives of American Art
- Talent Discovery Company, 1953-1957; Series 6; 0.9 Linear feet Boxes 115-116, 121
  This series contains mostly financial records for Talent Discovery Company, including check stub books, canceled checks, receipts, paid bills, and tax records. Also found are shipping records, correspondence, and inventory cards. Some correspondence is written in French.
  - Accounting Ledger, 1954-1956 (Box 115, Folder 12)
    Oversized material housed in Box 121, Folder 3
  - Banking Records, 1954-1956 (Box 115, Folder 13)
  - [Business and Tax Records], 1954-1956 (Box 115, Folder 14)
  - Canceled Checks, 1954-1956 (Box 115, Folder 15-17)
  - Check Stub Books, 1954-1956 (Box 115, Folder 18-19)
  - Correspondence, 1953-1956 (Box 115, Folder 20)
  - Inventory Cards, circa 1954-1956 (Box 115, Folder 21-22)
  - Ledgers [The Little Studio?], 1954-1956 (Box 115, Folder 23)
  - Miscellaneous Paper, 1954-1956 (Box 115, Folder 24)
  - Paid Bills, 1954 (Box 115, Folder 25)
  - [Paid Bills], 1954-1955 (Box 116, Folder 1)
  - Petty Cash Book, 1954-1956 (Box 116, Folder 2)
  - Petty Cash Receipts, 1954-1955 (Box 116, Folder 3)
  - Sales Receipts, 1954-1956 (Box 116, Folder 4)
  - Shipping, 1953-1955 (Box 116, Folder 5)
  - Tax Returns, 1954-1957 (Box 116, Folder 6)
  - Oversized Accounting Ledger, 1954-1956 (Box 121, Folder 3)
    Oversized material from Box 115, Folder 12
- Personal Papers of Lee Nordness, 1948-1976; Series 7; 0.7 Linear feet Box 116
  The Personal Papers of Lee Nordness includes records pertaining to Lee Nordness' involvement in the 140 East Tenants Cooperative, correspondence, a scrapbook, and scattered travel-related documents.
  - 140 East Tenants Corp., 1966-1975 (Box 116, Folder 7-18)
  - Apartment Ads, 1974-1976 (Box 116, Folder 19)
  - Biography, 1962-1965 (Box 116, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, 1965-1968 (Box 116, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, Craftsmen, 1966-1969 (Box 116, Folder 22)
  - Personal Appearances, 1962-1968 (Box 116, Folder 23)
  - Scrapbook, 1948-1961 (Box 116, Folder 24-25)
  - Travels, 1963-1968 (Box 116, Folder 26)